today will be different bro
how are you
then hit here Cara
it's christmas saw
tamo together
Go out to take care of your daddy there
the fraternization is going on
end of year of the high post Anchieta
and then I was invited bro
there's a barbecue
it's free
CONCERT?
the mother was inside the house
then the daughter was washing
washing the garage
and the father was not
the father had left
talks like this
O daughter
go ahead and call your dad in
then the girl with the hose like this
delay in understanding the joke
talk to me
what is the letter you thought
puts the other hand on top like this
now another hand on top
as soon as you turned a letter in your hand alone
top of present
merry christmas bro
I'm with brother
thank you for the gift
that's it bro
it's us guys you deserve bro
this atmosphere of fraternization
it's cute of the hour
but let's put what matters
so three days to finish this series
from tomorrow
no more mystery
begins to reveal to you what my business is
until tomorrow